module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'In what year was Netflix founded?', 
      a: '2002', 
      b: '1997',
      c: '1999',
      d: '2004',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who offered to buy-out Netflix in the year 2000?', 
      a: 'Barnes and Noble', 
      b: 'Sam Goody',
      c: 'Blockbuster',
      d: 'Accenture',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who founded Netflix?', 
      a: 'A couple of white dudes bc Silicon Valley', 
      b: 'Robot Overlords',
      c: 'Fred P. Accenture',
      d: 'Matty Wishnow',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What was Netflix\'s annual revenue for 2019?', 
      a: '$13.4 billion', 
      b: '$15 billion',
      c: '$18.2 billion',
      d: '$20.2 billion',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'In what year did Netflix begin offering streaming content?', 
      a: '2007', 
      b: '2008',
      c: '2009',
      d: '2010',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What was the 1st film distributed by Netflix?', 
      a: 'The Ridiculous 6', 
      b: 'Pee-wee\'s Big Holiday',
      c: 'Beasts of No Nation',
      d: 'The Do-Over',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What was the first program (show) distributed by Netflix', 
      a: 'Hemlock Grove', 
      b: 'House of Cards',
      c: 'Orange is the New Black',
      d: 'Bloodline',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'By the end of 2019, how many world-wide users did Netflix have?', 
      a: '167 million', 
      b: '140 million',
      c: '200 million',
      d: '102 million',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What Netflix film was the first ever to be nominated for Best Picture?', 
      a: 'The Irishman', 
      b: 'Marriage Story',
      c: 'Pee-wee\'s Big Holiday',
      d: 'Roma',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'When will The Office (US) no longer be available on Netflix?', 
      a: 'Aug 2020', 
      b: 'Now',
      c: 'Nov 2022',
      d: 'Jan 2021',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
};